# Henrique Ferreira

#### Web Developer

I am a Graphic Designer, who dared to venture into the codes and ended up falling in love! I consider that the main thing for any job is to have an open mind to all possibilities of learning. Curiosity about how the world works is what motivates me to always seek to learn and improve myself. I am punctual, assiduous, responsible, very communicative and very easy learning. I am moved by the contact between people and the exchange of experiences.

Guimarães - Portugal

+351927600909

henrique.f.dutra@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/hfdutra

instagram.com/henrique\_ferreira

Living in Portugual since 2016

# Henrique F.

## **Professional experience**

#### ForDesign SC 🖭 Web Developer 2016 - 2017Conceitos Diferentes 💿 Web Designer 2013 — 2016 Civil House of the State of Rio de Janeiro Graphic and Web Designer 2011 — 2013 Seven CGI ${\it Trainer\, Adobe\, Illustrator, Photoshop\, and\, In Design}$

#### **Education**

2013 — 2015	<b>MBA - Business Management</b> Universidade do Grande Rio • Brazil
2011 — 2013	<b>Higher Education in Marketing</b> Faculdade Gama e Souza • Brazil
2008 — 2012	<b>Graphic and Web Design</b> Seven Computação Gráfico • Brazil
2008 — 2010	<b>High School</b> Colégio Pedro II • Brazil

## **Skills**

HTML	Shopify	
CSS	Prestashop	
PHP	Adobe Illustrator	
Javascript	Adobe Photoshop	
Wordpress	Adobe InDesign	

#### Courses

2022	Front-end Engineer
2021	Wordpress Developer
2020	PHP to Wordpress
2016	Art Direction
2015	Digital Marketing